Guide to the Papers of Milo Guthrie, 1966-1987 RL.00488
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Periodicals, 1962-1987, undated 15 lin. ft.
  - NUC Newsletter (New University Conference), 1968-69 (Box 13)
  - Nuclear Times (Anti-Nuclear Weapons Movement), 1983, 1985 (Box 13)
  - El Nuevo Diario [Spanish language - "a new paper for a new man"], 1984 (Box 13)
  - Nukewatch, 1987 (Box 13)
  - Oberos En Marcha (Puerto Rican National Left Movement), 1980 (Box 13)
  - Off Our Backs [feminism], 1975, 1978-84 (Box 13)
  - On the Line (W.E.B. DuBois Clubs of America), 1969 (Box 13)
  - Open Road, 1978-82 (Box 13)
  - Opinion [Spanish language], 1980 (Box 13)
  - Organization of Arab Students Bulletin, 1973 (Box 13)
  - The Organizer (National Alliance Against Racist and Political Oppression), undated (Box 13)
  - Osawatomie (Weather Underground Organization), 1975 (Box 13)
  - Other Styles in Tennessee (Tennessee Valley Lesbain/Gay Authority), 1984 (Box 13)
  - Our Newsletter (People's Party), 1973-74 (Box 13)
  - Our Own [gay paper],1979-80, 1986 (Box 13)
  - Ours [feminist paper], 1979-80 (Box 13)
  - Outfront, ca. 1982 (Box 13)
  - Overthrow, 1979-85, 1987 (Box 13)
  - Pac-O-Lies (New York Media Project), 1969 (Box 14)
  - Palante (Young Lord's Party), undated (Box 14)
  - Palestine Focus (November 29th Coalition), 1983 (Box 14)
  - The Partisan (Youth Against War and Fascism), 1966-69 (Box 14)
  - The Party Line (People's Party), 1973-76 (Box 14)
  - Patria Libre, 1980, 1982 (Box 14)
  - Peace Action (Atlanta Peace Alliance), 1981 (Box 14)
  - Peace and Freedom (US Section of the Women's International League for Peace and Freedom), 1987 (Box 14)
  - Peace and Freedom Partisan (Peace and Freedom Party), 1971 (Box 14)
  - Peace and Freedom Party Newsletter, 1973 (Box 14)
  - Peace and Justice (Mid-South Peace and Justice Center), 1982 (Box 14)
  - Peace Courie r (World Peace Council), 1987 (Box 14)
  - Peace without Prisons (War Resisters League), 1981 (Box 14)
  - Peace Work (New England Peace and Social Justice), 1985 (Box 14)
  - The Peacemaker, 1975, 1978 (Box 14)
  - The People (Socialist Labor Party), 1980, 1983 (Box 14)
  - People and Land (Land Reform Movement), 1974 (Box 14)
  - People and Taxes (Tax Reform Research Group), 1973 (Box 14)
  - The People Factor, 1976 (Box 14)
  - The People Speak, undated (Box 14)
  - People's Alliance Bulletin, 1978 (Box 14)
  - People's Anti-War Mobilizer, 1981 (Box 14)
  - People's News Service, 1971 (Box 14)
  - People's Tribune, 1971-78, 1983 (Box 14)
  - The Peoples World, 1976 (Box 14)
  - Perspectiva Mundial [labor issues], 1982 (Box 14)
  - Philadelphia Resistance Review, ca. 1968 (Box 14)
  - The Phoenix (Southern Student Organization), 1968-69 (Box 14)
  - Plain Dealer, 1970, 1980 (Box 14)
  - Plenty, 1980-81 (Box 14)
  - Plexus [feminist paper], 1979-80, 1984 (Box 14)
  - Political Solutions (Democratic Socialists of America), 1986-87 (Box 14)
  - Por Esto!, 1982 (Box 14)
  - POSRIP Newsletter (People Organized To Stop Rape of Imprisoned Persons), 1980 (Box 14)
  - Post World War Council Newsletter, 1966 (Box 14)
  - Potemkin (American Servicemen's Union), 1970 (Box 14)
  - Potomac Alliance Power Plant, 1981 (Box 14)
  - Pow Journal [black issues], undated (Box 14)
  - The Powerline (Environmental Action Foundation), 1982 (Box 14)
  - The Progressive, 1980, 1983-84 (Box 14)
  - Progressive Labor (Progressive Labor Party), 1962, 1968-70 (Box 14)
  - Progressive Worker, 1973 (Box 14)
  - The Protean Radish, 1969-70 (Box 14)
  - Protect (Tennessee Environmental Council), 1987 (Box 14)
  - Pulse [gay magazine], 1984 (Box 14)
  - Quicksilver Times, 1969 (Box 15)
  - Radical America [Marxist journal], 1979 (Box 15)
  - The Radical and Populist (People's Party of Illinois), 1973 (Box 15)
  - A Radical Newspaper, 1969 (Box 15)
  - Ramparts, 1967-68 (Box 15)
  - Rap!, undated (Box 15)
  - Rat, 1968 (Box 15)
  - Ratlanta, 1983 (Box 15)
  - Ray O. Light Newsletter, 1983 (Box 15)
  - Realistic Living [religious paper], 1984 (Box 15)
  - Rebel Worker, 1980 (Box 15)
  - Rebellion News, 1967 (Box 15)
  - Red Dragon [prison issues/marxist--includes drafts indicating that Guthrie did some graphics work for this publication], 1980-1982 (Box 15)
  - The Red Papers, undated (Box 15)
  - Refugees [Central American issues], 1985 (Box 15)
  - Renewable Energy News, 1982 (Box 15)
  - Report to Presbyterians from Washington, 1987 (Box 15)
  - Resist, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Resistance (ISAUS-Student's National Union), 1978 (Box 15)
  - Resistance (League for Proletarian Revolution, Marx-Lenin), 1979 (Box 15)
  - Resistance: Documents and Analysis from the Illegal Front, 1982, undated (Box 15)
  - The Resistance Newsletter, 1967 (Box 15)
  - Resistencia, undated (Box 15)
  - Revolution (Revolutionary Communist Party, USA), 1974, 1978 (Box 15)
  - Revolutionary Communist Youth, 1980 (Box 15)
  - Revolutionary Marxist Caucus Newsletter, 1970 (Box 15)
  - Revolutionary Worker, 1979-81 (Box 15)
  - Revolutionary Youth Movement, ca. 1970-71 (Box 15)
  - RFD [gay men paper] 1980-82 (Box 15)
  - The Richmond Chronicle, 1969 (Box 15)
  - Rising Up Angry, 1970, nd (Box 15)
  - Rough Drafts (Berkeley Anti-Draft Association), undated (Box 15)
  - Rural Advance, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Rural America, 1977, 1981 (Box 15)
  - Rural Southern Voice For Peace, 1982, 1985-87 (Box 15)
  - Safe Harbor [health, ecology], 1978, undated (Box 15)
  - San Francisco's Appeal to Reason, 1983 (Box 15)
  - Sane World, 1969 (Box 15)
  - Santa Barbara News and Review, 1974 (Box 15)
  - Science for the People, 1977 (Box 15)
  - Scrap, 1985 (Box 15)
  - Secular Subjects, 1972 (Box 15)
  - The Sentinel [gay paper], 1981 (Box 15)
  - Series One, 1983 (Box 15)
  - Seven Days [nuclear issues], 1975-77, 1979-80 (Box 15)
  - Shakedown [servicepeople's issues], 1969 (Box 15)
  - Shut Down! [nuclear issues], ca. 1978 (Box 15)
  - Sing Out! [folk music magazine], 1975, 1977 (Box 15)
  - Sister Lode [feminist], 1983 (Box 15)
  - Sisters United [lesbian], 1979-80 (Box 15)
  - Soberinia (Central America and Caribbean Anti-imperalistic Tribune), 1982 (Box 15)
  - Socialist Forum (Socialist Committee of Correspondence), 1970 (Box 16)
  - Socialist Party Organizer (Socialist Party, USA), 1985 (Box 16)
  - Socialist Tribune (Socialist Party, USA), 1972-73, 1976-77, 1979-80, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Socialist Worker (International Socialist Organization), 1980 (Box 16)
  - Sojouner [feminist], 1979, 1982 (Box 16)
  - Solidaridad (El Salvador Bulletin), 1980 (Box 16)
  - Solidarity (Labor Committee of New York Students for a Democratic Society), 1969 (Box 16)
  - Somos [Spanish language--feminist paper], 1982 (Box 16)
  - Soul Force (Southern Christian Leadership Conference), 1968 (Box 16)
  - South End Press News, 1981 (Box 16)
  - South Vietnam in Struggle (South Vietnam National Front for Liberation Information Commission), 1969 (Box 16)
  - Southeast Asia Chronicle, 1980, undated (Box 16)
  - The Southern Advocate [black issues], 1978, 1981-82 (Box 16)
  - Southern Africa, 1975, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Southern Agitator [ecological issues], 1979-80 (Box 16)
  - Southern Alligator, 1979-80 (Box 16)
  - Southern Changes (Southern Regional Council), 1984, 1986 (Box 16)
  - The Southern Courier, 1968 (Box 16)
  - Southern Exposure, 1973 (Box 16)
  - Southern Feminist, 1984-87 (Box 16)
  - Southern Fight-Back/Southern Neighborhoods, 1980, 1985-87 (Box 16)
  - Southern Legal Action Movement, 1969-70 (Box 16)
  - The Southern Patriot (Southern Conference Educational Fund), 1968-75 (Box 16)
  - Southern Struggle, 1977-78, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee Handbook, 1968-69 (Box 16)
  - Space for People (Citizens for Space Demilitarization), 1980 (Box 16)
  - Spartacist [Marxist paper], 1968-70 (Box 16)
  - Spartacus [servicepeople's issues], 1969 (Box 16)
  - Spectrum: A Community View, 1981, 1983 (Box 16)
  - Spring Wine (Movement for a New Society), 1979 (Box 16)
  - The Split of the Weather Underground Organization, 1977 (Box 16)
  - Spirit of the People, 1976 (Box 16)
  - Stalinist Workers Group Bulletin, 1973 (Box 16)
  - The Storm!, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Strike!, 1982 (Box 16)
  - The Student Mobilizer, 1969 (Box 16)
  - Student Peace Union Bulletin, 1964 (Box 16)
  - Students for a Democratic Society New Left Notes, 1966, 1968-70 (Box 16)
  - Students for a Democratic Society View from the Outside, undated (Box 16)
  - The Sun Day Papers, 1978 (Box 16)
  - Survival Summer News (Mobilization for Survival), 1980 (Box 16)
  - Tattler Investigative Special, 1975 (Box 16)
  - Tell It Like It Is (Durham Health Workers and Patients), 1975 (Box 16)
  - Temple Free Press, 1969 (Box 16)
  - Tennessee Committee on Occupational Safety and Health--Health and Safety News, 1984 (Box 16)
  - Tennessee Environmental Report, 1985-86 (Box 16)
  - The Tennessee Gay Coalition for Human Rights, 1982-83 (Box 16)
  - Tennessee Grower, undated (Box 16)
  - Tennessee Hunger Coalition, 1986-87 (Box 16)
  - Tennessee Peace and Disarmament Campaign, 1987 (Box 16)
  - The Tennessee Valley Socialist (Socialist Party, USA), 1974-75 (Box 16)
  - Tennessee Voice of Labor, 1981 (Box 16)
  - Tennessee Volunteer, 1980 (Box 16)
  - The Tennessean, 1980-83 (Box 16)
  - Tennesseans for Keeping Abortion Legal and Safe Newsletter, 1982, 1984-87 (Box 16)
  - The Texas Observer, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Texas Women's Political Times, 1982 (Box 16)
  - Theater Work, 1981, 1983 (Box 17)
  - Thesmophoria/Themis, 1979-85 (Box 17)
  - Thought Crime, ca. 1985 (Box 17)
  - Through the Looking Glass [women and youth prison newsletter], 1979-80, undated (Box 17)
  - The Times They Are a Changin' (Bread and Roses Music Center), 1975 (Box 17)
  - Together, 1969 (Box 17)
  - Torch (Revolutionary Socialist League), 1984 (Box 17)
  - Undercurrents [energy/ecology issues], 1979 (Box 17)
  - Union W.A.G.E.: A Working Women's Newspaper (Women's Alliance to Gain Equality), 1980 (Box 17)
  - Unite! (Marxist-Leninist Organizing Committee), 1978, 1982 (Box 17)
  - The United Irishman, 1973 (Box 17)
  - United States Anti-Imperialist League, ca. 1983 (Box 17)
  - United States-China Report (US-China Peoples Friendship Association of Atlanta), 1975 (Box 17)
  - United States Farm News (US Farmer's Association), 1962, 1966, 1972-75, 1977-80, 1982-87 (Box 17)
  - Unity (US League of Revolutionary Struggle Marxist-Leninist), 1979-80, 1983 (Box 17)
  - Unity and Struggle, 1975 (Box 17)
  - University Employees Union News, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Uno Mas Uno, 1982 (Box 17)
  - Venceremos, 1983 (Box 17)
  - Veterans Stars and Stripes for Peace, 1967-68 (Box 17)
  - Vietnam Courier, 1969 (Box 17)
  - Vietnam GI, 1968 (Box 17)
  - Vietnam Summer News, 1967 (Box 17)
  - Vietnam Viewpoints, 1967 (Box 17)
  - Virginia Socialist, 1975 (Box 17)
  - The Voice of Eden, 1981 (Box 17)
  - The Voice of the Turtle (Bioregional Conference), 1986 (Box 17)
  - Voices (North Carolina State University), 1969 (Box 17)
  - Volunteer Left (Tennessee Democratic Socialists of America), 1984, undated (Box 17)
  - War Resisters League News, 1979-82, 1984 (Box 17)
  - War Resisters League Southeast Newsletter, 1980 (Box 17)
  - The Washington Blade [gay paper], 1983 (Box 17)
  - The Washington Free Press, 1968 (Box 17)
  - Washington Report (American Security Council), 1981 (Box 17)
  - The Washington Tribune, 1983 (Box 17)
  - Washington Watch, 1977 (Box 17)
  - Watchdog [labor issues], 1970 (Box 17)
  - Wave Upon Wave (Human Rights Party), undated (Box 17)
  - Ways and Means, 1982 (Box 17)
  - We the People, 1972 (Box 17)
  - Weekly People (Socialist Labor Party), 1965, 1967 (Box 17)
  - Welcome to San Francisco, 1984 (Box 17)
  - West Watch (Council for Inter-America Security), 1981-83 (Box 17)
  - The Western Socialist, 1967 (Box 17)
  - Western Worker, 1980 (Box 17)
  - What Is (New Age Activists), 1986 (Box 17)
  - Wildcat, 1969 (Box 17)
  - Win Magazine, 1972, 1975-82 (Box 17)
  - Winter Soldier (Vietnam Veterans Against the War/Winter Soldier Organization), 1974 (Box 18)
  - Wisconsin Commonwealth, 1985 (Box 18)
  - Wisconsin Patriot, 1973 (Box 18)
  - Witness for Peace Newsletter, 1984, 1986 (Box 18)
  - Woman News, 1980-81 (Box 18)
  - Woman's City-Country Chronicle, 1981 (Box 18)
  - Women Organizing (Socialist Feminist Commission of the New American Movement), ca. 1981 (Box 18)
  - Women's Free Express, 1974 (Box 18)
  - Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, 1973 (Box 18)
  - Women's Press, 1974 (Box 18)
  - Women's Source, 1981 (Box 18)
  - Women's World, 1985 (Box 18)
  - The Word is Out [lesbian paper], 1980 (Box 18)
  - The Word of New Orleans, 1969 (Box 18)
  - Work, 1981 (Box 18)
  - Work Force, 1974 (Box 18)
  - The Worker, 1966-68 (Box 18)
  - The Workers' Advocate, 1980, 1983 (Box 18)
  - The Workers' Tribune, undated (Box 18)
  - Workers Vanguard, 1977, 1979-80, 1983, undated (Box 18)
  - Workers Viewpoint, 1980-83 (Box 18)
  - Worker's World, 1969-70, 1980-83, 1985-86 (Box 18)
  - Worklist Mailing (Southern Student Organizing Committee), 1969 (Box 18)
  - World Goodwill Newsletter, 1984 (Box 18)
  - World Magazine, 1972, 1977 (Box 18)
  - World Revolution [Marxist-Leninist], 1970 (Box 18)
  - Yaveremos, 1981 (Box 18)
  - Yipster Times (Youth International Party News Service), 1978, undated (Box 18)
  - Young Lords Organization, 1970 (Box 18)
  - Young Socialist, 1975 (Box 18)
  - The Youth Liberation News Service, 1973 (Box 18)
  - Youth Magazine, 1976 (Box 18)
- Printed Material, 1966-1987, undated 4 lin. ft.
  Flyers, brochures, form letters, and bumper stickers document activities of liberal to radical left organizations. Arranged alphabetically by name of organization.
  - Act [working people in Durham, NC] (Box 19)
  - Ad Hoc Committee for a July 2 Emergency Mobilization (Central America) (Box 19)
  - Ad Hoc Gay Committee (Box 19)
  - African Liberation Day Coordinating Committee (Box 19)
  - African Liberation Support Committee (Box 19)
  - African Literature Education Project (Box 19)
  - African National Prison Organization (Box 19)
  - Alabama Conference for Gay Women and Men (Box 19)
  - Alice B. Toklas Democratic Club of Wake County [focus on discrimination laws] (Box 19)
  - All Africans Peoples Revolutionary Party [independent socialist party] (Box 19)
  - All-Beings Party [androgynous communism] (Box 19)
  - All Peoples Congress (Box 19)
  - Alliance Against Women's Oppression (Box 19)
  - Alternatives to Militarism, Inc. (Box 19)
  - American-Arab Anti-Discrimination Committee (Box 19)
  - American Civil Liberties Union (Box 19)
  - American Federation of Labor--Congress of Industrial Organizations (Box 19)
  - American Friends Service Committee: College Program (Box 19)
  - American Friends Service committee--Fellowship of Reconciliation (Box 19)
  - American Peace Test [anti-nuclear testing] (Box 19)
  - The Appalachian Alliance [response to massive flooding] (Box 19)
  - Appalachian South Folklife Center (Box 19)
  - Appalachian Student Health Coalition (Box 19)
  - Arno Press [political books] (Box 19)
  - Artists Restricting Tyranny (Box 19)
  - The Association for the Preservation of the Eno River Valley (Box 19)
  - The Association in Solidarity with Guatemala (Box 19)
  - Association of Libertarian Feminists (Box 19)
  - Association of Nicaraguan Women (Box 19)
  - Atlanta Coalition for the April Actions [Latin America, Africa, jobs and justice, and nuclear war] (Box 19)
  - Atlanta Gay Center (Box 19)
  - Atlanta Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam (Box 19)
  - Atlanta socialist Summer School (Box 19)
  - Atlanta Women's Union (Box 19)
  - Berkeley Women's Health Collective (Box 19)
  - Beverly Brown Dance Ensemble (Theater for Bodies and Voices) (Box 19)
  - Black August Organizing Committee (Box 19)
  - Black Hills Alliance [ecology] (Box 19)
  - Black Panther Party (Box 19)
  - Black Solidarity Committee (Box 19)
  - Bobby Hutton Health Brigade (Box 19)
  - The Bond (magazine promotion) (Box 19)
  - Bread and Roses Music Center [feminism] (Box 19)
  - Bureau of Public Secrets (Box 19)
  - Burning Spear Publications (magazine promotion and sale items) (Box 19)
  - Cambridge Documentary Films, Inc. [feminism] (Box 19)
  - Campaign For Safe Energy (Box 19)
  - California Liberation Alliance (Box 19)
  - California Voters for Choice Initiative Committee (Box 19)
  - Call Pamphlets (Communist Party) (Box 19)
  - Calvin Memorial Presbyterian Church Legal Defense Fund (Box 19)
  - Carolina Labor News (paper promotion) (Box 19)
  - Carolina Liberation Brigade (Box 19)
  - Center for Reflection on the Second Law (feminism) (Box 19)
  - Central America Solidarity Association (La Casa) (Box 19)
  - Central America Solidarity Committee (Box 19)
  - Central Committee for Conscientious Objectors (Box 19)
  - Cesar Cauce Publishers and Distributors, Inc. (Box 19)
  - Chapel Hill Revolutionary Movement (Box 19)
  - Chicago Area Draft Resisters (Box 19)
  - China books and Periodicals, Inc. (Box 19)
  - Christianity and Crisis (Christian Journal of opinion) (Box 19)
  - Circle [pagan religions, magic] (Box 19)
  - Citizens for Space Demilitarization (Box 19)
  - Citizens Helping to Achieve New Gains for Equality (Box 19)
  - Citizen's Party (Box 19)
  - Civil Rights Congress (Box 19)
  - Clergy and Laity Concerned (Box 19)
  - Cleveland Area Peace Action Council (Box 19)
  - Coalition Concerned About Human Rights in El Salvador (Box 19)
  - Coalition for a Free Central America (Box 19)
  - Coalition for a New Foreign and Military Policy (Box 19)
  - Coalition for a Non-Nuclear World (Box 19)
  - Coalition for a People's Alternative in 1980 (Box 19)
  - Coalition of Direct Action [peace] (Box 19)
  - Coalition to Oppose Autumn Forge 80 and All Imperialist War Preparations (Box 19)
  - Committee Against War and Imperialism (Box 19)
  - Committee for a Revolutionary Socialist Party (Box 19)
  - Committee for Gay and Lesbian Human Rights (Box 19)
  - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (Box 19)
  - Committee for National Liberation in the Middle East (Box 19)
  - Committee for the National Liberation Front of South Vietnam (Box 19)
  - Committee for the Presido 27 (Box 19)
  - Committee in Solidarity with the People of El Salvador (CISPES) (Box 19)
  - Committee of Greater Washington (Box 19)
  - Committee of Responsibility [anti-Vietnam War] (Box 19)
  - Committee of Returned Volunteers [anti-US imperialism in the East] (Box 19)
  - Committee of Solidarity with the People of Guatemala (Box 19)
  - Committee on Political Education (Box 19)
  - Committee to Aid American War Objectors (Box 19)
  - Committee to Aid the Defense of Robert F. Williams (Box 19)
  - Committee to Defend Imani and Stop the Death Penalty (Box 19)
  - Committee to Free the Mao Tse Tung Defendants (Box 19)
  - The Committee to Preserve Our Sexual and Civil Liberties (Box 19)
  - Committee to Stop Chemical Atrocities (Box 19)
  - Committees of Correspondence (Box 19)
  - The Communist League (Box 19)
  - The Communist Party (Box 19)
  - Communist Workers Party (Box 19)
  - Community Change Inc. [black liberation] (Box 19)
  - Community Friends School [Quaker education] (Box 19)
  - Comrades of the Black Workers Congress (Box 19)
  - Concerned Black Citizens (Box 19)
  - Concerned Falculty and staff Members at Colleges in North Carolina [draft resistance] (Box 19)
  - Concerned North and South Carolina Citizen's Committee (Box 19)
  - The Conference on Alternative State and Local Policies (Box 19)
  - Conference on Radical History (Box 19)
  - Congress of Racial Equality (CORE) (Box 19)
  - The Conservation Council of North Carolina [ecology] (Box 19)
  - The Conspiracy (Box 19)
  - Consumer Party (Box 19)
  - Corporate Information Center (Box 19)
  - Counter-Orientation (UNC - Protean/RADISH) [black liberation] (Box 19)
  - Counter-Surveillance Coalition (Box 19)
  - Country Fresh Farm Association (Box 19)
  - Cruise Missile Conversion Project (Box 19)
  - Cut Cane Associates [consulting group for working poor] (Box 19)
  - DC Moratorium Committee [anti-Vietnam War] (Box 20)
  - DC Student Committee on the Transportation Crisis (Box 20)
  - The Defense Committee (Box 20)
  - Democracy Project (Box 20)
  - Democratic Party (Box 20)
  - Democratic Socialists of America (Box 20)
  - Democrats for Change (Box 20)
  - Denver Botanic Gardens (Box 20)
  - Department of Health, Education, and Welfare (Box 20)
  - Dessie Woods Support Coalition (Box 20)
  - Dick Gregory Foundation Inc. (Box 20)
  - Disera (Box 20)
  - Donnelly/Colt [mail order company--buttons, bumper stickers, etc.] (Box 20)
  - Dry-Creek Co-operative Trading (Box 20)
  - Duke University Strike to Benefit Black Students, 1969 (Box 20)
  - Duke University Vigil for the Death for Martin Luther King Jr. (Box 20)
  - Durham County Citizen's Council (Box 20)
  - Durham Housing Struggle, 1966 (Box 20)
  - Dykes Against Racism (Box 20)
  - Dykes Opposed to Nuclear Technology (Box 20)
  - Earthwork (Box 20)
  - East Tennessee Vegetarian Society (Box 20)
  - East Village Organization for a Kinder Earth (Box 20)
  - Emerge [domestic violence] (Box 20)
  - Emergency Land Fund (Box 20)
  - Eno River Association (Box 20)
  - Equal Rights Congress (Box 20)
  - Equality Products [mail order company] (Box 20)
  - Eritrea Material Aid Campaign (Box 20)
  - Estamos Con el Sindicato! (Box 20)
  - Eugene V. Debs Foundation (Box 20)
  - The Faerie Circle (Box 20)
  - Farm Labor Organizing Committee (Box 20)
  - Farmers and Consumers (Box 20)
  - Fast for Life [anti-nuclear weapons] (Box 20)
  - Fellowship of Reconciliation (Box 20)
  - Ferne Sales and Manufacturing Co. (Box 20)
  - Fisk University Programs (Box 20)
  - Food First/Institute for Food and Development Policy [anti-US intervention in El Salvador] (Box 20)
  - Four Arrows [community group for Native Americans] (Box 20)
  - Freedom Now (Box 20)
  - Freedom Socialist Party and radical Cuomen (Box 20)
  - Freeze [anti-nuclear weapons] (Box 20)
  - Freeze Voter (Box 20)
  - Friends of the Filipino People (Box 20)
  - Friends of the Third World (Box 20)
  - FPSAT--Fuck the Public Schools Achievement Test (Box 20)
  - Gay Advocacy Project (Box 20)
  - Gay Anarchists (Box 20)
  - Gay Community/AIDS Project (Box 20)
  - Gay Community Services Center (Box 20)
  - Gay Draft Resistance Network (Box 20)
  - Gay Freedom Day Committee (Box 20)
  - Gay Men's Health Crisis (Box 20)
  - Gay Rights National Lobby (Box 20)
  - GI Civil Liberties Defense Committee (Box 20)
  - GIs United Against the War in Vietnam (Box 20)
  - Good Fairy Productions [gay men] (Box 20)
  - Good Neighbors Union [political party] (Box 20)
  - Government Resisters League (Box 20)
  - Grassroots Group of Second Class Citizens (Box 20)
  - Green Politics (Box 20)
  - Ground Zero Club (Box 20)
  - The Guardian (Box 20)
  - Gulf Boycott Coalition (Box 20)
  - Gulf Coast Pulpwood Association (Box 20)
  - Hatian Refugee Center (Box 20)
  - Haymarket Democratic Club (Box 20)
  - Helaine Victorian Press, Inc. [postcards of women] (Box 20)
  - High School Mobilization (Box 20)
  - High School Student Union (Box 20)
  - Highlander Research and Education Center (Box 20)
  - Hopi Indian Nation (Box 20)
  - Human Rights Festival 1986 (Box 20)
  - Human Rights Party (Box 20)
  - Ikesdatter Press (Box 20)
  - In Context [movement for a positive sustainable future] (Box 20)
  - Independent Party (Box 20)
  - Individuals Against the Crime of Silence (Box 20)
  - The Indochina Peace Campaign (Box 20)
  - Industrial Workers of the World (Box 20)
  - Infant Formula Action Coalition (Box 20)
  - Institute for Democratic Socialism (Box 20)
  - Institute for Social Ecology (Box 20)
  - Intact Educational Foundation (Box 20)
  - Inter-Religious Task Force (Box 20)
  - International Chemical Workers Union (Box 20)
  - International Committee Against Racism (Box 20)